arrangeyourvacation.com 2010-12-30

# ArrangeYourVacation.com - Privacy policy

Privacy Policy 

Privacy Policy 

[ ArrangeYourVacation.com](http://arrangeyourvacation.com/) is serious about protecting the privacy of our owners and our renting visitors. We use information collected about you only to process and bill orders and to make our Web site a more useful and valuable service. We respect the privacy of those who visit or become advertisers. Our privacy policy is stated below, but please be aware that should you follow a link on our Web site to another Web site, you are no longer covered by this policy. It is a good idea to understand the privacy policy of any Web site before sharing personal information with it.

Your Information: What, How, and Why?

Property Owners/Advertisers and Vacation Planning Visitors

In order to process a request you may have, we need to know contact information that could include all or some of the following: your full name, address, telephone number, e-mail address, and, in the case of an advertising listing, a method of payment. Vacation Rentals will use this information to contact you from time to time with critical customer updates and information, or to send you information about new services or opportunities. You will be able to "unsubscribe" and not receive marketing information, but we must always be able to e-mail you critical information about your account and our mutual business relationship.

Your information is not shared with third parties, except: 1) in the case of special promotions by ArrangeYourVacation, or one of its partners, about which you"ve requested to be notified; 2) where a third party performs services on behalf of ArrangeYourVacation and has agreed to keep such information confidential (such as the processing of your credit card payment or the conduct of an online survey for example); and 3) the aggregate use of the information of multiple ArrangeYourVacation advertisers and visitors where individual personal information is not disclosed. ArrangeYourVacation shares Web site usage information about advertisers and visitors with a third-party tracking company for the purpose of reporting statistics. ArrangeYourVacation also uses your information to market its services and to gain feedback on potential new services.

Newsletters

As an advertiser or visitor to [ArrangeYourVacation.com](http://arrangeyourvacation.com/), you will receive either or both of our Owner or Traveler newsletters. You may cancel your subscription to these newsletters at any time.

Surveys 

Surveys are another method by which we gather information about our visitors. From time to time, we request owner or newsletter subscribers" input in order to evaluate potential features and services. The decision to answer a survey is completely yours. We use information gathered from surveys to improve our service.

Inquiries

Site visitors may send inquiries to our property owners/advertisers via clickable links on ArrangeYourVacation listings. If you choose to send an inquiry through these links, your personal information, including your e-mail address and any other information you supply, will be visible to the owner of the property you inquired about so that they might reply to you. Do not share information in the e-mail that you are not prepared to allow them to have, including, but not limited to, credit card and bank account information. These inquiries are sent to both the individual owner/advertiser you selected and retained by ArrangeYourVacation. The resulting inquiry is available for review only by the owner/advertiser to whom they were initially addressed and to ArrangeYourVacations customer service employees, who may be asked by advertisers for their past inquiry information. While the content of these inquiries is not shared with any other party, [ArrangeYourVacation.com](http://arrangeyourvacation.com/) may, from time to time, use third party e-mail servers to send and track receipt of the inquiry e-mails, and analyze the pattern of inquiry usage via these third party tracking systems.

How Do We Protect Your Information Once We Have It?

All personal information is stored on a secure server. We do NOT ask you for credit card numbers and we do NOT store credit card information. All such information is stored by 2CO our credit card processing partner, on their secured servers, and is protected via its proprietary methods.

Click here (<https://www.2checkout.com/documentation/privacy.htm>) to read the 2CO privacy policy.

What is a Cookie and Why Do We Use Them?

A "cookie" is a small piece of information sent by a Web server to store in a Web browser so that it can later be read back from that browser. [ ArrangeYourVacation.com](http://arrangeyourvacation.com/) may uses cookies to store some personal preferences for your future visits. Cookies allow us to recognize you more quickly; therefore, your time spent on our site can be more personalized and productive. You"ll find that cookies are an industry standard and are used at most major Web sites in much the same way we use them here at ArrangeYourVacation.

We use third-party site usage tracking companies to analyze your Web site visit or to conduct surveys. In the course of serving our pages, these third parties may place or recognize a unique "cookie" on your browser. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, e-mail address or telephone number) about your visits to [ArrangeYourVacation.com](http://arrangeyourvacation.com/) and other Web sites in order to help us understand how to serve you better.

By using our Web site and signing up for ArrangeYourVacation services, you consent to the collection and use of the previously mentioned information by ArrangeYourVacation and our affiliates. This policy is subject to change without notice. Privacy issues represent a growing concern for all Web users. To keep up-to-date with our policies, please check this page frequently. We reserve the right to change, modify, add, or remove portions of this policy at any time.

Contact Information

In the event of questions about access to your Personal Information or Prospect Information; our collection, use, management, or disclosure of Personal Information or Prospect Information; or this Privacy Statement, contact us at: 

Privacy Officer

SDC-BG Ltd 

ul. Goliama mogila 44 

kw. Kinocentur (Bojana) 

1616 Sofia 

BULGARIA

Effective Date

This Privacy Statement is effective as of January 1, 2008. 

VERSION 1.0
